

Azam Firdaus Bin Ahmad Yaziz

Backend Developer

INTRODUCTION

I am a skilled backend developer with 5 years of expertise in maintaining and building a reliable software solution with proficiency in language/-framework such as PHP, Java, Ruby, and Vue.js.

My strongest assets would be in crafting efficient problem solving algorithm

LANGUAGES

Bahasa Melayu

Native

English

Highly proficient in speaking and in writing

SKILLS

PHP/Laravel

Javascript

Ruby/Ruby on Rails

Java

REFERENCE

Amirul Naim Bin Ahmad Nazri Senior Software Developer

amirulnaim.ahmadnazri@gmail.com +60175592120

Dr. Norhanim Bte Abdul Samat
Pensyarah Kanan (DS52)
Jabatan Timbalan Naib Canselor
(Hal Ehwal Pelajar)
norhanim@utm.my
+607 553 7282

KEEP IN TOUCH

Phone

Email

+60 12 589 0745

azamfirdausmpm@gmail.com

Phone

Website

linkedin.com/in/azam-firdaus-ahmad-yaziz/

https://azam-firdaus.github.io/

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Software Engineering | Sep 2016 - Sep 2019 Universiti Teknoloogy Malaysia, Johor

Courses took:

- 1. Software Engineering
- 2. Java
- 3. Object Oriented Programming
- Diploma in Computer Science (Information Technology) | Jun 2013 Apr 2016

Universiti Teknoloogy Malaysia, Kuala Lumpur

Courses took:

- 1. C++
- 2. Java
- 3. Assembly

EXPERIENCE

Back End Developer | July 2022 - Present
Boneybone Ventures Sdn Bhd

Responsible for working with team members to develop and maintain company's software/system primarily using Laravel, VueJS, Live-wire, SQL

Web Developer | Oct 2020 - Jun 2022 Ujilari Studio, Johor

Work as web developer to develop website in PHP/Laravel Framework based on user requirement.

Intern | Jul 2018 - Jan 2019 RN Technologies Sdn Bhd, Johor

Intern as a web developer where barebone PHP is the majorly used language to develop the backend of the website develop while interning at the company.

Intern | Nov 2016 - Mar 2016 Ezera Tech, Penang

Intern as mainly web developer with some minor software development. Ruby/Ruby on Rails were used almost exclusively to develop website.